

PERSONAL

Birthday : 27th January 1992

Relationship : Single Nationality : Indian

Languages : English, Malayalam,

Hindi, Tamil

SKILLS

Communication Creativity Teamwork Organization Leadership Team Player

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML **JavaScript** CSS Angular Vue.js React.is Jasmine Selenium Unity3D

C.# Java MySQL **PostgreSQL** MongoDB

Apache Jmeter

Jenkins

C++

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe XD

CONTACT



+91 7012880183



aghiljv@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/aghil-jose



https://aghiljv.github.io/

AGHIL JOSE Full Stack Engineer

PROFILE

A versatile Software Engineer with experience in End-to-End Application Development and have worked with Accenture and Nissan Digital LLP. I specialize in building application to the needs of the business and clients in Agile Environment. Experienced in Automotive visualization and virtual testing environment for Autonomous vehicles. A team player with strong interpersonal skills, with the ability to collaborate with multi-functional teams.

EDUCATION

MCA

UNIVERSITY OF KERALA College of Engineering Trivandrum 2014-2017

B.SC PHYSICS

UNIVERSITY OF CALICUT MES Kalladi College, Mannarkkad Palakkad, Kerala 2010-2013

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

September 2018-Present

Nissan Digital India LLP | www.nissan-global.com

Developed an application to help calculate whether a particular car model will be economically feasible for the company if manufactured using Angular and Spring Boot.

Roles & Responsibilities

- Work with the business and vendors to understand the requirements and procedures.
- Develop and take responsibility of the application end-to-end.
- Work with the testing team in end-to-end testing.

Developed UI for a Proof of Concept Application to help the customer to decide the car model best suited for their lifestyle using Angular.

Developed highly interactive UI of a Proof of Concept Application for the Product Planning Team using ElectronJS and VueJS.

These brought the attention of business and have been turned into products.

Developed a highly Dynamic Autonomous Simulation Environment for cars with near Photo-realism usina Unity 3D.

Roles & Responsibilities

- Understand the current business requirements and standards in the autonomous vehicle space.
- Collaborate with a cross functional team.
- Collect and process relevant data.
- Solve complex mathematical problems.

Associate Software Engineer

January 2018 - June 2018

Accenture | www.accenture.com

Gained knowledge in automated testing tools such as **Selenium**, **HP UFT** and **Apache Jmeter**.

TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS









































REFERENCES

Narendran Janardhanan

Technical Lead / Nissan Digital India LLP T. +91 9895778000 E. narendran.js@gmail.com

Kripesh Krishnadas

Product Manager/ Nissan Digital India LLP T. +91 9840990661 E. kripeshpkd@gmail.com